# Mariusz Krzesiński

## **HELLO!**

My name is Mariusz Krzesiński and I am an 25 years old Student of Applied Informatics at Wyższa Szkoła Zarządzania i Bankowości in Kraków. I am committed to develop in areas of new technologies to bring my interests to proffessional life.



### **EDUCATION** -

WSZIB KRAKÓW: MSc Applied Informatics (exp. 2017)

Studies program focused on IT side of Business Intelligence and its appliance in Management.

JAN KOCHANOWSKI UNIVERSITY: BACHELOR of Science in Logistics 2014

IStudies program focused on building of konwledge foundation in areas of  $modern\ transportation,\ procurement,\ management\ and\ coordination.$ 

# JOB EXPERIENCE-

SALES ASSISTANT: BP Partners 2012 - 2015

Daily maintenace and coordination of sales activities for BP gas station.

SALES ASSISTANT: FHU Łukasz Wtorek 2010-2012

Direct sales activities.

RETAIL CUSTOMER CONSULTANT: CCIG 2010-2010

Direct sales activities.



- 🤨 Al. Jana Pawła II 35/100, Kraków
- <u>^</u> +48 790 601 608
- krzesinskimariusz@gmail.com

### SKILLS-

Communication

Teamwork

Creativity

Taking Responsibility

Humor